The Filipino revolution that even Marcos couldn't crush!
Machete Maidens Unleashed! is a documentary film directed by Mark Hartley.
In the final decades of the 20th century, the Philippines was a country where low-budget exploitation-film
producers were free to make nearly any kind of movie they wanted, any way they pleased.
It was a country with extremely lax labor regulations and a very
permissive attitude towards cultural expression.
As a result, it became a hotbed for the production of cheapie movies.
Their history and the genre itself are detailed in
this breezy, nostalgic documentary.
Self, played by Roger Corman.
Self, played by Colleen Camp.
Self, played by John Landis.
Self, played by Sid Haig.
Self, played by R. Lee Ermey.
Self, played by Joe Dante.
Machete Maidens Unleashed!
is a 2010 Australian documentary film directed by Mark Hartley.
The film explores themes of exploitation, interview,
philippines, b movie, little people.